Now let's go and explore another AWS service in the area of natural language processing
called as Amazon Transcribe. So Amazon Trustcribe is a service that converts speech to text.
And earlier we had seen Amazon Poly which converts text to speech and it does the reverse.
Speech to text. Now let's see how this works. So you have Amazon Transcribe service and you
provide the input as speech and it generates a text file. Now let's take a look at some of the
common use cases for Amazon Trustcribe. So the first one is medical transcription. So you can convert
the conversation between a physician and a patient into text. So the next one is call center
analytics and agent assist. So through Transcribe what you can do is you can convert to text
the conversation between the customer and the agent. Then later you can run analytics on top of
the text that you have captured. So you can do sentiment analysis, you can look at the gap analysis
and so on. And then finally it can also detect toxic content in audio for online gaming social media
or peer-to-peer conversation or voice conversation. Now let's go to the console and check out this
Amazon Transcribe service. So I'll just go and search for Transcribe and here is Amazon Transcribe.
So let me now just click on this created transcript and on the right hand you can see
start streaming. So when I click on start streaming and say something it's going to convert it into
text. So if you just click on this welcome to our course on Udemy. So you can see it's converted
this voice into text and now on the left hand side you can see Amazon Transcribe call analytics.
This is where you can convert the conversation between the agent and the customer and then do
analytics. So you can do a real-time analytics or you can do post call analytics. So if you just
click on this and here it shows you can create a job and then run the analytics. Similarly then you
have the Amazon Transcribe medical. You can do the real-time transcription. So if you just click on
this. So you can either capture the conversation between the clinician and patient or it can also
do a dictation. So use for post medical encounter dictation. So if I just click on this and now you
can just click on start streaming and as you speak it's going to convert that speech into text.
Okay that's pretty much it from this lecture. I'll see you in the next lecture. Thank you.